Guide to the Sarah G. Jacobson Papers MSS.157
Fales Library and Special Collections
Katz, Steven D. Film Directing Shot by Shot: Visualizing from Concept to Screen. Studio City, CA: Michael Wiese Productions, 1991.
Kaufman, Lloyd and James Gunn. All I Need to Know About Filmmaking I Learned from the Toxic Avenger. New York: Berkley Boulevard Books, 1998.
Klein, Joe. Woodie Guthrie: A Life. New York: Ballantine Books, 1986.
L
Lair Robinson, Barbara and Rick Lair Robinson. "If My Dad's a Sexaholic, What Does That Make Me?" Minneapolis: ComCare Publishers, 1991.
Lamarr, Hedy. Ecstasy and Me: My Life as a Woman. New York: Fawcett Crest Books, 1967.
Larkin, Rochelle. The Beatles: Yesterday…Today…Tomorrow. New York: Scholastic Book Services, 1974.
Leblanc, Lauraine. Pretty in Punk: Girls's Gender Resistance in a Boys' Subculture. New Brunswick, NJ: Rutgers University Press, 1999.
Lennon, John. In His Own Write and A Spaniard in the Works. New York: Signet Books, 1965.
Linklater, Richard. Slacker. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1992.
Lipton, Lenny. Independent Film Making. New York: Fireside, 1983.
Living Sober: Some Methods A.A. Members Have Used for Not Drinking. New York: Alcoholics Anonymous World Services, 1999.
Lloyd, Carol. Creating a Life Worth Living. New York: HarperCollins, 1997.
Lloyd, Nancy. Simple Money Solutions: 10 Ways You Can Stop Feeling Overwhelmed by Money and Start Making It Work for You. New York: Times Business, 2000.
Lynch, Peter and John Rothchild. Learn to Earn: A Beginner's Guide to the Basics of Investing and Business. New York: Fireside Books, 1995.
M
Maguire, Gregory. Wicked: The Life and Times of the Wicked Witch of the West. New York: Regan Books, 1995.
Maio, Kathi. Feminist in the Dark: Reviewing the Movies. Freedom, CA: The Crossing Press, 1988.
Maio, Kathi. Popcorn and Sexual Politics. Freedom, CA: The Crossing Press, 1991.
Malkiewicz, Kris. Cinematography. New York: Prentice Hall Press, 1989.
Malkiewicz, Kris. Film Lighting. New York: Prentice Hall Press, 1986.
Manning, Sarra. Guitar Girl. New York: Dutton Children's Books, 2004.
Mass Murderer 1999 Calendar.
McKeown, Charles and Terry Gilliam. The Adventures of Baron Munchausen. New York: Applause Theatre Book Publishers, 1989.
McNeil, Legs and Gillian McCain. Please Kill Me: The Uncensored Oral History of Punk. New York: Grove Press, 1996.
Meir, Golda. My Life. New York: Dell Books, 1975.
Mellody, Pia. Facing Love Addiction: Giving Yourself the Power to Change the Way You Love. San Francisco: HarperCollins, 1992.
Miller, Henry. Tropic of Cancer. New York: Grove Press, 1999.
Murch, Walter. In the Blink of an Eye. Los Angeles: Silman-James Press, 2001.
The Murder Can Be Fun 1995 Datebook, 1994.
Murder Can Be Fun Presents (Anti-) Sex Tips for Teens: The Teenage Advice Book: 1897- 1987, 2 copies.
N
Nakken, Craig. The Addictive Personality: Understanding Compulsion in Our Lives. San Francisco: Harper and Row, Publishers, 1988.
Nerve, May-June 2000 (premiere issue), March-April 2001.
Nin, Anais. The Diary of Anais Nin, Volume Two 1934 - 1939. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1967.
Nin, Anais. The Diary of Anais Nin, Volume Three 1939 - 1944. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1969.
Novello, Don. Citizen Lazlo!: The Lazlo Letters Volume 2. New York: Workman Publishing, 1992.
Novello, Don. The Lazlo Letters! New York: Workman Publishing, 1992.
O
O'Brien, Lucy. She Bop: The Definitive History of Women in Rock, Pop and Soul. New York: Penguin Books, 1996.
O'Donnell, Peter. Modesty Blaise. New York: DC Comics, 1994.
O'Donnell, Peter. Modesty Blaise: First American Edition Series. # 1, 5.
P
Pandemonium, #3, 1989.
Pang, May and Henry Edwards. Loving John. New York: Warner Books, 1983.
Paths to Recovery: Al-Anon's Steps, Traditions, and Concepts. Virginia Beach: Al-Anon Family Groups, 1997.
People Weekly, vol. 36, no. 13, October 7, 1991; vol. 40, no. 20, November 15, 1993.
People Weekly: Extra, Spring 1991.
Perry, Joan and Dolores Barclay. A Girl Needs Cash: How to Take Charge of Your Financial Life. New York: Times Business, 1997.
Perry, Tim and Ed Glinert. Fodor's Rock and Roll Traveler USA. New York: Fodor's Travel Publications, 1996.
Pincus, Edward and Steven Ascher. The Filmmaker's Handbook. New York: Plume Books, 1984.
Playboy, vol. 39, no. 9, 1992; vol. 41, no.3, 1994.
Popcorn, Faith and Lys Marigold. EVEolution: Understanding Women - Eight Essential Truths that Work in Your Busiqness and Your Life. New York: Hyperion, 2000.
Popcorn, Faith and Lys Marigold. EVEolution: Understanding Women - Eight Essential Truths that Work in Your Busiqness and Your Life. New York: Hyperion, 2000.
Punk, # 0, Winter 2001.
R
Raphael, Amy. Grrrls: Viva Rock Divas. New York: St. Martin's Griffin, 1995.
Re/Search, #11, 1987.
Re/Search, #13, 1991.
Rich, Doris, L. America Earhart: A Biography. Washington, D.C.: Smithsonian Institution Press, 1989.
Richards, Andrea. Girl Director: A How-to Guide for the First-time Flat-broke Film Maker (and Video Maker). Chicago: Girl Press, 2001.
Rollerderby Presents Generation L.
Rollins, Henry. Get in the Van: On the Road with Black Flag. Los Angeles: 2.13.61 Publications, 1994.
Rosenkrantz, Linda and Pamela Redmond Satran. Beyond Jennifer and Jason: An Enlightened Guide to naming Your Baby. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1990.
Rossi, Melissa. Courtney Love: Queen of Noise. New York: Pocket Books, 1996.
S
Sapphire. Push. New York: Vintage Books, 1997.
Savage, Jon. England's Dreaming: Sex Pistols and Punk Rock. London: Faber and Faber, 1991.
Schrag, Ariel. Potential. San Jose, CA: SLG Publishing, 2000.
Schroeppel, Tom. The Bare Bones Camera Course for Film and Video. Tampa, FL: Tom Schroeppel, 1989.
Scr(i)pt, September/October 1996.
Seger, Linda. Making a Good Script Great. New York: Dodd, Mead and Company, 1987.
Sex and Love Addicts Anonymous. Boston: The Augustine Fellowship, 1986.
Shahan, Lynn. Living Alone and Liking It: A Complete Guide to Living on Your Own. New York: Warner Books, 1982.
Singleton, Ralph S. Film Budgeting: Or, How Much Will it Cost to Shoot Your Movie? Los Angeles: Lone Eagle Publishing, 1996.
Somerville, Mollie. Eleanor Roosevely As I Knew Her. McLean, VA: EPM Publications, 1996.
Spiegelman, Art. Maus I: A Survivor's Tale: My Father Bleeds History. New York: Pantheon Books, 1986.
Spin, vol. 17, no. 5, May 2001.
Sragow, Michael, Ed. Produced and Abandoned. San Francisco: Mercury House, 1990.
Star Jam Comics, 3 issues.
Star Wars Insider, # 23.
Sturges, Preston. Preston Sturges by Preston Sturges. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1990.
T
Thompson, Hunter S. Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas: A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream. New York: Vintage Books, 1971.
Thompson, Peg and Saeko Usukawa. The Little Black and White Book of Film Noir: Quotations From the Films of the 40s and 50s. Vancouver: Arsenal Pulp Press, 1992.
Truffaut, Francois. Hitchcock. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1985.
TV Star Costume, n.d.
Twelve Steps and Twelve Traditions. New York: Alcoholics Anonymous World Services, Inc., 2001.
V
Vachon, Christine. Shooting to Kill: How an Independent Producer Blasts Through the Barriers to Make Movies That Matter. New York: Avon Books, 1998.
W
Waters, John. Shock Value: A Tasteful Book About Bad Taste. New York: Delta Books, 1985.
Wiener, Jon. Come Together: John Lennon in His Time. New York: Random House, 1984.
Wise, Nick. Kurt Cobain and Courtney Love in Their Own Words. London: Omnibus Press, 1996.
Wuh, Hank C.K. Sexual Fitness: 7 Essential Elements to Optimizing Your Sensuality, Satisfaction, and Well-being. New York: Perigree Books, 2001.
X
X, Malcolm. The Autobiography of Malcolm X. New York: Ballantine Books, 1989.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596, with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Rock music -- United States -- 1991-2000; Punk culture.; Riot grrrl movement.; San Francisco (Calif.); New York (N.Y.).; Chicago (Ill.); Alternative rock music.; Independent filmmakers.; Fanzines.; Film festivals.; Film criticism.; Anders, Allison; Sundance Film Festival; Kuchar, George, 1942-; New York Underground Film Festival; Station Wagon Productions; Chicago Underground Film Festival; Davis, Tamra; Dowd, Nancy, 1945-
- Series I: I Was A Teenage Serial Killer
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I contains materials related to the production and distribution of Jacobson's film, I Was A Teenage Serial Killer. Includes script, film stills, media, distribution. See Oversize for related material.
  - Subseries A: Production Materials
    Subseries A contains materials relating to the production of I Was A Teenage Serial Killer. This includes the script, mock-ups and film stills.
    - "Creative Stuff": Early Script Draft of I Was a Teenage Serial Killer, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Serial Killer: Film Stills, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Serial Killer: Titles, Mock-Ups, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Serial Killer: Kinkos Brown Bag, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Serial Killer: Final Track Flow Chart, related to media item 157.0114A, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: Press and Distribution
    Subseries B: Press and Distribution, contains materials created for the promotion and distribution of I Was A Teenage Serial Killer. Includes orignal flyers, press pack and reviews. See Oversize for related material
    - Serial Killer: Original Flyers, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Serial Killer: Press Pack, Photo Album, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Serial Killer: Letter to Comedy Central, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Serial Killer: Free Speech TV, Contract, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Serial Killer: Art Rage, Austrailia, Invoice, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Serial Killer: Press, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Serial Killer: Film Screenings, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Serial Killer: New York Underground Film Festival, Pass, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Serial Killer: Review: Film Arts Foundation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Serial Killer: Review, Essential Cinema, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Serial Killer: Review, Fizz Magazine, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Serial Killer: Walker Art Center, Summer Camp, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Serial Killer: Review, Film Threat Video Guide, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Serial Killer: Review, The Nose, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Serial Killer: Review, Film Threat Video Guide, #14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Serial Killer: Review Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Serial Killer: Review, The Ladies Art Review, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Subseries C: Media Originals
    Subseries C: Media Originals, contains media items related to I Was A Teenage Serial Killer. Access copies may not be available for consulation, please ask a Fales archivist.
    - Serial Killer: Reel 1 of 1, 16mm Access Film Print, 1992; ID: 157.0005 (Reel 157.0005)
    - Serial Killer: Reel 1 of 3, 16mm Magnetic Final Track, 1992; ID: 157.0114A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 157.0114A)
    - Serial Killer: Reel 2 of 3, 16mm Magnetic Final Track, 1992; ID: 157.0115A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 157.0115A)
    - Serial Killer: Reel 3 of 3, 16 mm Magnetic Final Track, 1992; ID: 157.0116A (Shelf Media, Media ID: 157.0116A)
    - Serial Killer: "Sarah Channel 2 PBS Interview -- 4/3/94," I Was A Teenage Serial Killer, 1992; ID: 157.0224 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0224)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements Note
      Format: Video Recording (VHS), Donated Element
      TRT: Unknown
    - Serial Killer: "Sarah Jacobson -- Arts On 2, 3/30/94: Starts at 7: Sarah at 7:25", 1994; ID: 157.0232 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0232)
    - Serial Killer: "Sarah Jacobson -- Last Segment, Arts On 2 Interview, 3/30/94", 1994; ID: 157.0233 (Box 33, Media ID: 157.0233)
  - Subseries D: 2018 Accretion
    Scope and Contents
    Subseries D: 2018 Accretion production materials from her independent film project I Was a Teenage Serial Killer.
    - Teenage Serial Killer shirt, Undated (Box 40)
- Series II: Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore
  Series II contains materials related to the production and distribution of Jacobson's film, Mary Jane's Not A Virgin Anymore. Quotation marks are used to indicate Jacobson's original folder title. See Oversize for related material.
  - Subseries A: Production Materials
    Subseries A: Production Materials, contains materials related to the production of the feature film including film reports, script detailing, editing reports, and administrative documents.
    - Mary Jane: Script, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Mary Jane: Film Arts Foundation Grant Letter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Mary Jane: Insurance Policy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Mary Jane: Non-Profit Agreement, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Mary Jane: Proposed Budget, Crew List, Gear List, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Mary Jane: Release Form, Lisa Berstein, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Mary Jane: "Mary Jane Cast Stuff", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Mary Jane: Cast Releases, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Mary Jane: Cast Releases, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Mary Jane: Location Releases, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Mary Jane: "Sarah's Notes for MJNAVA," Folder 1 of 6: Set Maps, Character Placements, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Mary Jane: "Sarah's Notes for MJNAVA," Folder 2 of 6: Victoria Theatre Schedule, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Mary Jane: "Sarah's Notes for MJNAVA," Folder 3 of 6: Shooting Call, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34.1)
    - Mary Jane: "Sarah's Notes for MJNAVA," Folder 4 of 6: Scenes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Mary Jane: "Sarah's Notes for MJNAVA," Folder 5 of 6: Crew List, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Mary Jane: "Sarah's Notes for MJNAVA," Folder 6 of 6: Scene Notes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Mary Jane: "Camera Reports Virgin", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Mary Jane: "Camera Reports Virgin," Original Binder, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Mary Jane: Film Trim and Documents from Mos Roll #6. Related to media item 157.005A, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Mary Jane: "Lab Reports/Gibb's Neg Notes/Lab Shit." Folder 1 of 3: Processing Invoices, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Mary Jane: "Lab Reports/ Gibb's Neg Notes/Lab Shit." Folder 2 of 3: Lab Reports, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Mary Jane: "Lab Reports/Gibb's Neg Notes/Lab Shit." Folder 3 of 3: Camera Roll Logs, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Mary Jane: "Lab Reports and Gibb's Neg Notes/Lab Shit." Original Binder, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43.1)
    - Mary Jane: Sound, Folder 1 of 4: R-1, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Mary Jane: Sound, Folder 2 of 4: R-2, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Mary Jane: Sound, Folder 3 of 4: R-3, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Mary Jane: Folder 4 of 4, R-4, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Mary Jane: Sound: Wild Track/Room Tone Log, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Mary Jane: Sound Mix, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Mary Jane: Sound Reports, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Mary Jane: "Log Book, Dailies and More!" Folder 1 of 4: Edgecode Use Log, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Mary Jane: "Log Book, Dailies and More!" Folder 2 of 4: Edit Log, Sync Rolls, Wild Track Master, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Mary Jane: "Log Book, Dailies and More!" Folder 3 of 4: Edit Logs, MOS Roll, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Mary Jane: "Log Book, Dailies and More!" Folder 4 of 4: Dailies Pull Sheets, Camera Roll Logs, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Mary Jane: "Log Book, Dailies and More!" Original Binder, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Mary Jane: Camera Report, Notes and Lab Documents, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Mary Jane: Timing Strip Chart and Note, related media item 157.0078A, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Mary Jane: Plastic Bag with Annotations, related to media item 157.0079A, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Mary Jane: Note from Dean Martison for Optical Titles, related to media item 157.0081A, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Mary Jane: Timing Strip and Receipt for Film Element, related to media item 157.0082A, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Mary Jane: Negative Confirming documents, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Mary Jane: "Additional Dialogue Recording," Recording and Writing Notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Mary Jane: "Additional Dialogue Recording," Notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Mary Jane: "Additional Dialogue Recording," Recording and Cutting Notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Mary Jane: "Additional Dialogue Recording," Notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Mary Jane: "Dialogue Notes", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Mary Jane: "Post-Production: Skywalker", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Mary Jane: F/X and Foley Notes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Mary Jane: Titles, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Mary Jane: Lab Documents, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Subseries B: Distribution and Public Relations
    Subseries B: Distribution and Public Relations Materials, includes materials related to the promotion and distribution of the feature film including original flyers, orders and press packs.
    - Mary Jane: Non-Profit Application, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Mary Jane: Press Pack and Bio, Folder 1 of 4, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Mary Jane: Press Pack and Bio, Folder 2 of 4, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Mary Jane: Press Pack and Bio, Folder 3 of 4, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Mary Jane: Press Pack and Bio, Folder 4 of 4, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Mary Jane: Originals for Mock-ups and Postcards, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Mary Jane: Copies of Press Materials, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Mary Jane: Release Form, Original Flyers, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Mary Jane: Framed Ticket of Screening at Chicago Underground Film Festival, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Mary Jane: "Publicist New York", 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Mary Jane: "Mary Jane Questionaires", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Mary Jane: "MJ Guest List Premiere", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Mary Jane: "Sundance Variety Bomb", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour," Box Office (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Mary Jane: "Image 5129," Press Release, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Mary Jane: "MJ Tapes to get Back" Distribution List, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Mary Jane: " UCLA/Sundance Archive" Donation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Mary Jane: "LA Landmark Invoice", 1999 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Mary Jane: "LA Landmark," Correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Mary Jane: "Orders", 2003 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Subseries C: Festivals and Conferences
    Subseries C: Festivals and Conferences, contains calendars, passes and flyers for film festivals that the feature film screened at.
    - Mary Jane: "IFFU'95," Conference, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Mary Jane: "Cold Spring," Conference, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Mary Jane: "Cold Spring Workshop," Conference, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Mary Jane: "Gibbs Chapman, Cinematheque", 1995 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Mary Jane: "Chicago Underground Film Festival", 1995 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Mary Jane: "IFFM," Conference, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Mary Jane: IFFCON, Conference, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Mary Jane: IFFCON Badge/Pass, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Mary Jane: Chicago Underground Film Festival, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" Badges/Pass, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" SXSW Badge/Pass, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" IFFM Badges and Passes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" Maryland Film Festival Pass, undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" Masses Pass, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" IFFCON 1997 Schedule (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Mary Jane: "USA Festivals" Walker Art Center Agreement, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Mary Jane: "European Tour" Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Mary Jane: "European Tour" Helsinki Film Festival Pass, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Mary Jane: "Sundance '97" Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Mary Jane: "Sundance '97" Correspondence and Schedule, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Mary Jane: "Sundance '97" Publicist DAA, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Mary Jane: "Sundance '97" Festival Guest Past, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Mary Jane: Atlanta Film Festival Badge, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Mary Jane: "Festival Calenders, Book Shelf MJ", 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour Alabama" Invoice and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Anchorage, Alaska" Invoice (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Valley Art, Arizona" Profile, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Atlanta, Larry Thomas" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Bijou" Invoice, Profile, Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Cleveland Filmakers" Invoice and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Crest Sacramento" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Dobie" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Hartford CT" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Cinema Arts, Huntington NY,31" Invoice and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Iowa" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Kansas City" Flyer (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, LA Publicity" (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Maryland" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Mills College" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Minnesota" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Madison, WI" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, New York, Cinema Village" Invoice and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, New York Cinema Village, Flyer, Ticket" (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Parkland, Oakland," Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Olympia WA" Correspondence and Calender (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Phyllis Kauf, Phial Intl Houses" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Phyllis Kauf, Phial Intl Houses" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Seattle" Profile (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Vancouver" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, East Coast College, Weselyan" Invoice and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Mary Jane: "1998 Tour, Taiwan" Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 142)